Guide to the Meredith Tax papers, 1956-2016 RL.01275
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Organizational Materials, 1958-2013; 130 boxes
  - Cairo planning meeting, 1997 (Box 60)
  - Eva Hung (Box 60)
  - Anchee Min (Box 60)
  - Nanda Witharanage (Box 60)
  - Yu Mi, 1997 (Box 60)
  - Zhao Mei (Box 60)
  - China (Box 60)
  - Zhu Hong (Box 60)
  - Ye Wen-ling (Box 60)
  - Leila Ahmed (Box 60)
  - Anisa Darwish (Box 60)
  - Tahmineh Milani (Iran, film) (Box 60)
  - Anna Politkovskaya (Box 60)
  - Gao Zhan (Box 60)
  - Malihe Maghazei (Box 60)
  - Kumari - Sri Lanka, 2004 (Box 60)
  - Women and Memory (Egypt) (Box 60)
  - Kawther Salaam, 2006 (Box 60)
  - Mona Ali (Egypt) (Box 60)
  - The Arab Women's Solidarity Association by Peter Hitchcock (Box 60)
  - Kawther Salam, '02 (Box 60)
  - International PEN (Box 60)
  - Veronique Tadjo (Box 61)
  - Seble Dawit (Box 61)
  - Miriam Tlali (Box 61)
  - African network meeting, list, report (Box 61)
  - Aminata Sow Fall (Box 61)
  - Vuyo Wagi (Box 61)
  - Meredeth Turshen, conference reports re: peace (Box 61)
  - Louisa Mogudi (Box 61)
  - Miriam Tlali, 1997 (Box 61)
  - Patricia McFadden (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Tanzania (Box 61)
  - Magaya vs. Magaya (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - FAMWZ proposal Zimbabwe, 2000 (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - International PEN (Box 61)
  - Tsitsi event, 1999 (3 folders) (Box 62)
  - Asenath (2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Africa program expenses and receipts (Box 62)
  - African Women's Writers Programme (Box 62)
  - FEM-ART Kenya minutes etc. (Box 62)
  - E. Africa Program, 1997 (Box 62)
  - Asenath Bole Odaga, 1997 (Box 62)
  - Asenath, 1999 (Box 62)
  - Dan Connell Corresp., 2000 (Box 62)
  - Kenya (Box 62)
  - Pan-Africa Work (Box 62)
  - Africa programming (Box 63)
  - GADECE - Kenya (Box 63)
  - Asenath correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 63)
  - Africa program/Budgets, 1997 (Box 63)
  - Africa program, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Zimbabwe International Book Fair, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Sarah Mkhonza, Cities of Asylum, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Isioma Daniel, FFE, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Yari Yari meeting - Women's WORLD network (Box 63)
  - OWWA (Box 63)
  - Yari Yari (Box 63)
  - RELAT, 2000 (Box 63)
  - Latin American Program, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Margo Glantz Shapiro, Women's WORLD Membership form (Box 63)
  - UNESCO Conference, Lima, Peru, April 15-20, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Cuba (Box 63)
  - International PEN (Box 63)
  - Maria Arrillaga (Box 64)
  - Angelica Gorodischer (Box 64)
  - Merle Hodge (Box 64)
  - Cristina de Fonesca (Box 64)
  - Magda Arce (Chile) (Box 64)
  - Zimbabwe International Book Fair (Box 64)
  - Harare Bookfair/Workshop 1996 (Box 64)
  - ZIBF Meredith/WW Bookfair (Box 64)
  - Africa Expenses, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Meredith Dianne Travel Docs. (Box 64)
  - Africa Program Proposal, 1999 (Box 64)
  - South African Women's Health Project (Box 64)
  - Publications for ZIBF/S. Africa (Box 64)
  - Three year project for Africa (Box 64)
  - Program at Zimbabwe International Book Fair, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Gertrude Fester (Box 64)
  - Africa (Box 64)
  - Cape Town/Gertrude Fester (Box 64)
  - Beverly Jansen - WEAVE, Cape Town (Box 64)
  - FEMRITE Proposals, 1999 (Box 64)
  - FEMRITE Workshop report and receipts (Box 65)
  - FEMRITE - Uganda, 1995-1998 (Box 65)
  - Sarah Mkhonza, 2001-2004 (4 folders) (Box 65)
  - FEMRITE, 2002-2003 (Box 65)
  - WEAVE (Box 65)
  - Cameroon (Female Assoc. Writers in Cameroon) (Box 65)
  - Lina Magaia, 1997 (Box 65)
  - MBAASEM, 2002 (Box 65)
  - Ama accounts MBAASEM, 2000 (Box 65)
  - Bea Campbell Case, 2000 (Box 66)
  - Campbell Jones Fund (Box 66)
  - Russian Program (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Svetlana's book, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Vesna Kesic (Box 66)
  - Orlanda (Germany) (Box 66)
  - Svetlana Slapsak (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Nadya, 1997-1998 You and Me (Box 66)
  - PEN International (Box 66)
  - Flip chart poll (Box 67)
  - Questionnaire (Box 67)
  - UN-Beijing, 1995 (Box 67)
  - WW Literature for Beijing (Box 67)
  - Beijing (3 folders) (Box 67)
  - Logistics (Box 67)
  - CSA Platform for action, 1994 (Box 67)
  - International PEN (Box 67)
  - Notebooks, 1995-2000 (Box 68-70)
  - Brochures (Box 71)
  - Women's WORLD, 1996 (Box 71)
  - World March of Women, 1999 (7 folders) (Box 71)
  - For Bd mailing (Box 71)
  - Publications (Box 71)
  - Women's WORLD (Box 72)
  - Asenath assessment, 1998-1999 (Box 72)
  - Vitas new WW board members, 1999 (Box 72)
  - Two cloth banners (Box 73)
  - Dianne (Box 74)
  - Board memos (Box 74)
  - Culture, development and human rights meeting, 1996 (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Women's WORLD (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Women's WORLD (4 folders) (Box 75)
  - NEWW re: Beijing (Box 75)
  - Sisterhood is Global Institute (Box 75)
  - Women's WORLD (Box 76)
  - Clippings (Box 76)
  - NGO Forum on Women Beijing, 1995 (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - Beijing protest (Box 76)
  - Accreditation problems (Box 76)
  - Women's Tribune Center, Beijing publication (Box 76)
  - OSI Conference, Almaty 11/01 (Box 77)
  - Conferences and Events - Current (Box 77)
  - DSL, 2001 (Box 77)
  - Just Peace Technologies website, 2001 (Box 77)
  - Egrants.org (Box 77)
  - Donate Now/Egrants (Box 77)
  - Website postcard (Box 77)
  - Hostmysite.com and network solutions (Box 77)
  - Letterhead design (Box 77)
  - Identity design '01 (Box 77)
  - Preliminary website notes, proposals, June 2001 (Box 77)
  - Debby Dreer (Box 77)
  - Website info 1999 (Box 77)
  - Women's WORLD (3 folders) (Box 77)
  - Women's WORLD (5 folders) (Box 78)
  - Zimbabwe Book Fair brainstorming meeting flip chart, 1999 (Box 78)
  - Ms. Fdn AWID grant (Box 79)
  - AWID Conference, 2005 (Box 79)
  - Current human rights, censorship (Box 79)
  - Ford human rights, Close to Home (Box 79)
  - India and Russian proposal, 2003 (Box 79)
  - Leona (Box 79)
  - Scholars Rescue Fund (Box 79)
  - Art (Box 79)
  - Dress codes (Box 79)
  - Bring the world home, 2003 (Box 79)
  - US Conference, 2003 (Box 79)
  - Women's WORLD Leadership training institute, Cape Town, 2004 (Box 79)
  - From AWID conference (Box 79)
  - Sharbari Ahmed (Box 79)
  - Anne Flaherty (prisoner) (Box 79)
  - Ericka Duncan/Sag Harbour School (Box 79)
  - WILL lists and reading list (Box 79)
  - World March of Women, 2000 (Box 79)
  - Feminist Expo 2000 (Feminist Majority) (Box 79)
  - Poor people's world summit to end poverty (Box 79)
  - National Women's Studies Assoc. (Box 79)
  - Info Packet/Research, 1998 (Box 81)
  - Attacks on Women's Studies - Research (Box 81)
  - HIVOS '98 (Box 81)
  - Events CUNY 12/4-5/00 (Box 81)
  - Possible venues for parties and events (Box 81)
  - CUNY panel, women's voices and New European order, 2000 (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Medicine show reading, 2001 (Box 81)
  - Tsitsi Dangarembga, 1999 (Box 81)
  - Afghan women's program, 2001 (Box 81)
  - Barbara Omolade, CWE (Box 81)
  - Distribution: Power the Word II (Box 81)
  - Contracts for European pamphlet translations/editions (Box 81)
  - ISBN#s (Box 81)
  - Women's WORLD Book, 1999 (Box 81)
  - Publishing handbook for Caribbean women writers (Box 81)
  - Publications program/web (Box 81)
  - National women's studies association conference, 1999 (Box 81)
  - Mutual aid for writers (Box 81)
  - Haley farm (Box 81)
  - FFE 1995-2001 (4 folders) (Box 81)
  - WW Institute (Box 81)
  - Conference centers (Box 81)
  - Grants and fellowships (Box 81)
  - World march of women (Box 81)
  - WW Mission and program flyer (Box 81)
  - Donna's Michigan Conf, Feb 99 (Box 81)
  - Clippings (Box 81)
  - Meredith's (Picture) Cartoon (Story) (Box 81)
  - Welfare Rights Initiative (Box 81)
  - AWID Forum, 2002 (Box 82)
  - Voices Program (Box 82)
  - WRI Course Final Report, 2000 (Box 82)
  - Women's WORLD - WILL Proposal Packet (Box 82)
  - US Program, 1999 (Box 82)
  - WILL (Box 82)
  - Najwa Makhoul, 1999 (Box 82)
  - Crisis articles (Box 82)
  - NCAC (Box 82)
  - Wartime Censorship (Box 82)
  - Afghani Ams NYC (Box 82)
  - WTFC commentaries, 9/11/2001 (Box 82)
  - NEWW-OSI Crisis meeting, 2001 (Box 82)
  - Tabitha Walrund Case, 1999 (Box 82)
  - Brecht Forum Speech and List re: CWPE Book (Box 82)
  - Media lists - press (Box 83)
  - Marjorie Lightman (Box 83)
  - North American Correspondence (Box 83)
  - Jayne Cortez (Box 83)
  - Alice Walker (Box 83)
  - Dangerous Intersections Conference (Box 83)
  - Julie Nsanzurwimo (Box 83)
  - Stone Soup (Box 83)
  - Ms. article, 1997 (Box 83)
  - Week of Resistance (Box 83)
  - Rona Fields (Box 83)
  - Yari-Yari (Box 83)
  - Ad Women's Review of Books, 1997 (Box 83)
  - Audre Lorde award, Union Institute (Box 83)
  - Fund for Women Artists (Box 83)
  - Kitchen table press, 1997 (Box 83)
  - Speech Columbia Seminar w/Nesta (Box 83)
  - Salzburg Seminars (Box 83)
  - Media and Democracy, 1997 (Box 83)
  - WW Institute CUNY, 2000 (Box 83)
  - Institute-School proposal, Nesta and me, 1998 (Box 83)
  - Global Women's Movement clips (Box 83)
  - Women's WORLD (2 folders) (Box 83)
  - Newsday Op Ed New Paltz conference, 1997-1998 (3 folders) (Box 84)
  - AT&T Foundation, 2000 (Box 85)
  - Academy for Educational Development (Fellowship for Zohra), 2002 (Box 85)
  - Altman Foundation, 2000 (Box 85)
  - Andy Warhol (Box 85)
  - Armstrong (Box 85)
  - Asia Foundation, 1994 (Box 85)
  - Lily Auchincloss (Box 85)
  - Avon Products Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 85)
  - Banyan Tree Foundation, 2002 (Box 85)
  - Heinrich Boll Fdn, 2001 (Box 85)
  - Boehm Foundation, 1992-97 (Box 85)
  - Bydale Foundation, 2000 (Box 85)
  - Christensen Fund (Box 85)
  - Robert Sterling Clark, 1997 (Box 85)
  - Compton Foundation, 1998 (Box 85)
  - Cowles Charitable Trust (Box 85)
  - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 2001 (Box 85)
  - Drue Heinz Trust, 2000 (Box 85)
  - Dobkin Family Fdn, 2001 (Box 85)
  - Ford Foundation, 1993-2000 (7 folders) (Box 85)
  - Ford Barbara Sullivan, 2000-2001 (Box 86)
  - Ford report #980-0786-1, 2002 (Box 86)
  - Ford - Aaron Back (Box 86)
  - Finnish Ministry of Foreign Affairs (Finnida), 1997-2001 (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Firedoll Foundation (Box 86)
  - Foundation for a Compassionate Society: General Information (Box 86)
  - Fundraising Invites (Box 86)
  - Funding Exchange, 1993-4 (Box 86)
  - George Family Foundation, 2001 (Box 86)
  - Ford Proposal, 2001-2004 (3 folders) (Box 86)
  - HIVOS, 1996-97 (Box 86)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1997-1999 (3 folders) (Box 86)
  - Kepa, 2001 (Box 86)
  - Albert A. List Foundation, 1997-2001 (Box 86)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 86)
  - Global Fund for Women, 1998 (Box 86)
  - Global proposal sent to European donors, 2001 (Box 86)
  - Global Catalyst Fdn (Box 87)
  - Global Fund for Women, 1992-1994 (Box 87)
  - Goldman Sachs, 2000 (Box 87)
  - HKH Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 87)
  - HIVOS, 1998-2000 (Box 87)
  - IBM, 1997-1998 (Box 87)
  - Jewish Fund for Justice, 2000-01 (Box 87)
  - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1992-2000 (4 folders) (Box 87)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 2000 (Box 87)
  - Mama Cash (Box 87)
  - MacMillan Foundation, 1993 (Box 87)
  - Match International, 1997 (Box 87)
  - Moriah Fund, 2003 (Box 87)
  - Charles S. Mott Foundation, 1996-2002 (2 folders) (Box 87)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1996 (Box 87)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women/Campbell Jones grant, 1997-2001 (3 folders) (Box 87)
  - Anne F. Murray, 1996 (Box 87)
  - New World Foundation, 2000 (Box 87)
  - Naisjarjestot (National Council of Women in Finland), 2001 (Box 88)
  - New York Community Truest, 2000-2001 (Box 88)
  - New York Friends Grp., 1993-1995 (Box 88)
  - Norad, 2001 (Box 88)
  - New York Women's Foundation (Box 88)
  - North Star Fund, 2000 (Box 88)
  - Norman Fdn (Box 88)
  - Peter Norton Fdn (Box 88)
  - Novib, 1996-2001 (3 folders) (Box 88)
  - Open Meadows Proposal, 2003 (Box 88)
  - OSI, 2000-2003 (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Open Society Institute, 1996-2000 (8 folders) (Box 88)
  - Patrina Foundation, 2001 (Box 88)
  - Pforzheimer Foundation 2000 (Box 88)
  - Prince Claus Fund, 2001 (Box 88)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1999-2001 (4 folders) (Box 88)
  - Ruasing Trust, 1998-99 (Box 88)
  - Real Networks Foundation, 2001-02 (Box 88)
  - Reek Foundation, 1995 (Box 88)
  - Robin Hood Foundation, 2000 (Box 88)
  - Ellyn Rosenthal, 1997 (Box 88)
  - May and Samuel Rudin (Box 88)
  - Rubin Foundation, Chernobyl Project, 1996-2001 (Box 88)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1991-2000 (12 folders) (Box 89)
  - H. Rubenstein Foundation, 2000 (Box 89)
  - Rubin Foundation, 1992-2001 (Box 89)
  - Scherman Foundation, 2000 (Box 89)
  - SCO-CAF, 2001 (Box 89)
  - Shaler Adams Foundation, 1994-99 (3 folders) (Box 89)
  - The Sister Fund, 1993-2001 (2 folders) (Box 89)
  - Streisand Foundation, 1997-98 (Box 90)
  - Surdna Foundation, 2000 (Box 90)
  - Swedish Agency for Int'l Devt. Cooperation (SIDA), 2000-2001 (Box 90)
  - UNESCO, 1993-2000 (5 folders) (Box 90)
  - Threshold (Box 90)
  - Three Guineas Fund (Box 90)
  - Tides Foundation, 1994-2000 (2 folders) (Box 90)
  - Tinker Foundation (Box 90)
  - UNIFEM, 1992-1994 (Box 90)
  - Urgent Action Fund (Box 90)
  - Katrina Vanden Heuval, 1994-1997 (Box 90)
  - Wendling Foundation, 2000 (Box 90)
  - Working Assets, 2001 (Box 90)
  - Annual appeal 1999-2004 (8 folders) (Box 91)
  - Direct mail, general (Box 91)
  - Individual appeals, 1999-2000 (2 folders) (Box 91)
  - Appeal contributions 2002 (Box 91)
  - Egrants.org, 2002 (Box 92)
  - Appeal: Letter, stats, list info, 2002 (Box 92)
  - Mailing houses, sample appeals (Box 92)
  - Fundraising appeal - for lists and info (Box 92)
  - Lists and names to think about (Box 92)
  - WW donors and list (Box 92)
  - Financial notes, 2003 (Box 92)
  - Mailing for outreach/network/funding, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Concept paper for Fdns (Box 93)
  - Budgets and work sheets, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Funding notes, 1994 (Box 93)
  - Funding application, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Ford Fdn center (Box 93)
  - Turndowns - try again (Box 93)
  - Lit - WW and IPWWC (Box 93)
  - Lael Stegall (Box 93)
  - Speaking contract (Box 93)
  - CD - Human rights educ. (Box 93)
  - Research - partners (Box 93)
  - Pamph shipping, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Our Own Press (Box 93)
  - Press Lists (Box 93)
  - European pamphlet (Box 93)
  - New European Order pamphlet (Box 93)
  - Women's Voices and the New European Order (Box 93)
  - Articles by Meredith Tax (Box 93)
  - Women's WORLD Fundraising Plans, 1995 (2 folders) (Box 93)
  - Funding - people, lists (Box 93)
  - Foundation packet, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Women's WORLD Party, 1994 (Box 94)
  - Conference on Gender-Based Censorship (Box 94)
  - Gender-based censorship, 1996 (Box 94)
  - Draft proposal to the Ford Foundation (Box 94)
  - Pamphlet for Beijing, 1994-1995 (6 folders) (Box 94)
  - Bellagio, 1996 (3 folders) (Box 94)
  - Women's WORLD (Box 94)
  - Gender-based censorship, 1996 (Box 95)
  - Bellagio Travel and Milan Hotel, (7 folders) (Box 95)
  - Foundation packet materials (Box 95)
  - CUNY Continuing Education and Public Programs (Box 95)
  - "A Women's WORLD Bouquet" - Zimbabwe International Book Fair, 1999 (Box 95)
  - Board retreat and business meeting, 2000 (Box 95)
  - Women's WORLD (Box 95)
  - Women's WORLD annual appeal, 2006-2008 (3 folders) (Box 96)
  - WW Financials, 2009 (Box 96)
  - Hammett Hellman, 2006 (Box 96)
  - Web stats, 2006 (Box 96)
  - Website upgrade, 2006 (Box 96)
  - Conversation Street (Box 96)
  - TechSoup.org (Box 96)
  - Connect US (Tides Fdn) proposal, 2006 (Box 96)
  - Audit of Women's WORLD, 2005 (Box 96)
  - Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 96)
  - Public Support - Grants and Contributions, 1999-2003 (Box 96)
  - Tax Exempt certificates, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Women's WORLD incorporation documents and amendments (Box 96)
  - IRS 501(c)(3) determination letter (Box 96)
  - Information re: incorporation, tax status from other groups (Box 96)
  - Women's WORLD Incorporation/bylaws (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - Incorporation papers, 1995 (Box 97)
  - Articles of incorporation, bylaws, and amendments (Box 97)
  - Lawyers Alliance for NY, 1993 (Box 97)
  - NY State ST 119 Application (Box 97)
  - IRS 501(c)(3) application (Box 97)
  - Tax exempt certificate - copies (Box 97)
  - United Nations: NGO Section application for consultative status, 1997-1998 (3 folders) (Box 97)
  - UNESCO affiliation, 1998-1999 (Box 97)
  - UN Beijing (Box 97)
  - Connect US (Tides), 2004 (Box 97)
  - Greenwall Foundation (Box 97)
  - Tech Grants, 2004 (Box 97)
  - Gere Foundation (Box 97)
  - Jerome Foundation (Box 97)
  - Mayer Foundation (Box 97)
  - Puffin Foundation (Box 97)
  - Mertz-Gilmore, 2004 (Box 97)
  - Barbara Streisand Fdn (Box 97)
  - Oprah Winfrey Fdn (Box 97)
  - Foundation notes and research, 2004 (Box 97)
  - Furthermore publishing program (J.M. Kaplan Fdn) (Box 97)
  - Women's WORLD grant research, 2002 (Box 97)
  - Columbia Foundation (Box 97)
  - Heathcote Art Foundation (Box 97)
  - Do thank yous (Box 97)
  - IRS correspondence and notes, 2005 (Box 97)
  - Penelope Boehm, 2006 (Box 97)
  - Lutz and Carr, 2006 (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - IRS, 2006 (Box 98)
  - Ragged Edge Press, 2006 (Box 98)
  - Meredith Tax, 2006 (Box 98)
  - WW trip Russia and London, 2006 (Box 98)
  - Verizon, 2006 (Box 98)
  - Chase Vista, 2006-7 (Box 98)
  - Chase deposits, 2006 (Box 98)
  - Chase Bank Visa, 2006 (Box 98)
  - Chase line of Credit, 2006 (Box 98)
  - IRS return, 2005 (Box 98)
  - US PO Box, 2006 (Box 98)
  - Staples Business Advantage/Non-profit coordinating committee of NY: Order form (Box 98)
  - Tax forms (Box 98)
  - Women's WORLD Board meeting, 2003 (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - War zones - correspondence with winners (Box 98)
  - Proposal and LOI Writing materials, 2001 (Box 98)
  - Notes re: fdns, prospects, 2000 (Box 99)
  - Board Mtg., 2002 (Box 99)
  - Retreat overview (Box 99)
  - Board mailings and email, 2001 (Box 99)
  - Affiliations, 2001 (Box 99)
  - Strategic planning notes, 2000 (Box 99)
  - Support center - Vogelsang, 1999-2000 (Box 99)
  - Hammett-Hellman Awards, 1993 (Box 99)
  - Fundraising for Social Change excerpt (Box 99)
  - Women's WORLD US board meeting, 2002 (Box 99)
  - Meredith (Box 99)
  - Women's WORLD Foundation Packet, 2002 (Box 99)
  - Women's WORLD printed lit, brochure, 2003 (Box 99)
  - Notebook (Box 99)
  - Board meeting online, 2001 (Box 99)
  - EC meeting, 2001 (Box 99)
  - Board retreat notes, 2000 (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Minutes, programs, and reports (Box 99)
  - Fact checking material for website (Box 99)
  - Angelica Gorodischer (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Annamaria (Box 99)
  - Grace, 1999-2000 (Box 99)
  - Joan, 1999-2000 (Box 99)
  - Mariella, 1999-2002 (4 folders) (Box 100)
  - Micere Mugo (Box 100)
  - Paula, 1999-2000 (Box 100)
  - Nadia, 1999-2000 (Box 100)
  - Ritu Menon, 1999-2000 (Box 100)
  - Board retreat notes and minutes, 2000 (Box 100)
  - Board mailings and including emails, 2000 (Box 100)
  - EC Meeting mailing, 1999 (Box 100)
  - Mailing to Women's WORLD board, 1999 (Box 100)
  - Mailing to EC, 1999 (Box 100)
  - Women's WORLD Institute San Marcos, 2007 (Box 100)
  - Reports on San Marcos PEG collaborative program (Box 100)
  - Gila's list of Jewish donors (Box 100)
  - Office space, 2001 (Box 100)
  - Office and board, 2001 (Box 100)
  - To Do/But not pressing (Box 100)
  - Nadya Azhgikhina (Box 101)
  - The Women's Dialogue (Box 101)
  - Russian-language pamphlet (Box 101)
  - Bellagio meeting notes, 1998 (Box 101)
  - Europe - organizing work (Box 101)
  - WW e-mail prop (Box 101)
  - FTM Agency, Rights and Writers from Russia (Box 101)
  - Sara (Swedish PEN) (Box 101)
  - Russian PEN (Box 101)
  - Chernobyl (Box 101)
  - Russian texts (Box 101)
  - Vyi i Myi (Box 101)
  - Svetlana Alexievitch, Chernobyl (4 folders) (Box 101)
  - Earnings (Box 102)
  - European team packet (Box 102)
  - Women's WORLD European team meeting at Bellagio (Box 102)
  - Christiana Lambrinidis (Box 102)
  - Monica Nagler (Box 102)
  - Rebecca Gomperts (Box 102)
  - Paris Conference (Box 102)
  - Women, Culture, and Development Practices Conference (Box 103)
  - Kosovo - Motrat Qiriazi (Box 103)
  - Jurga Ivanauskaite (Box 103)
  - European Pamphlet (Box 103)
  - Kosovo War, 1999 (Box 103)
  - Sasha Sviridova (Box 103)
  - Toril Brekke (Box 103)
  - Susanne Possing (Box 103)
  - Leslie Kaplan (Box 103)
  - Monica Nagler Wittgenstein (2 folders) (Box 103)
  - Joanne Leedom-Ackerman (Box 103)
  - Denisa Comenescu (Box 103)
  - European Correspondence (Box 103)
  - Centrum Kobiet, Cracow Poland (Box 103)
  - Christiana Lambrinidis (Box 103)
  - War Zones, 2003-2007 (Box 104)
  - War zones, 2003 (7 folders) (Box 105)
  - Women's Voices in War Zones Contest, master list (Box 105)
  - Press files Haggai (Box 105)
  - Deborah Drier, 2003 (Box 106)
  - Chase checking account, 2005 (Box 106)
  - Bank One/Chase, 2005 (Box 106)
  - Reimbursement, M. Tax, 2005 (Box 106)
  - Chase Vista, 2005 (Box 106)
  - AWID Forum Expenses (Box 106)
  - Lutz and Carr, 2005 (Box 106)
  - USPS mailing permit (Box 106)
  - Deposits Women's WORLD 2005 (Box 106)
  - Boehm, 2005 (Box 106)
  - Verizon, 2005 (Box 106)
  - Appeals, 2005 (Box 106)
  - Audit File (Box 106)
  - Unemployment, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Schwab accounts (Box 106)
  - Chase checking account, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Chase Vista, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Bank One Credit Card Statements, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Boehm business services, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Verizon, 2004 (Box 106)
  - US Postal Service, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Paychex, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Lutz and Carr, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Bank One Credit Card Receipts, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Chase deposits, 2004 (Box 106)
  - Audit, 2004 (Box 106)
  - WW Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 106)
  - Audit File, 2002 (Box 106)
  - Lutz and Carr, 2003 (Box 106)
  - Smith College Women's WORLD Course 2001-2002 (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Smith Kahn Seminar program, 2003 (Box 106)
  - Unemployment, 2004 (Box 106)
  - AWID, 2003 (Box 106)
  - Africa programs (Box 107)
  - Minutes board of director, 1st meeting, 1994 (Box 107)
  - New York Women's Foundation grant application (Box 107)
  - By Laws (Box 107)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1999 (Box 107)
  - Executive Committee Report (Box 107)
  - Board meeting NYC, 1999 (Box 107)
  - Marjorie Agosin, 1997 (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Ama Ata Aidoo (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Women's WORLD (Box 107)
  - Ama Ata Aidoo, 1997 (Box 108)
  - Paula Gidding (Box 108)
  - Kali for Women (Box 108)
  - Ritu Menon, 1997(2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Grace Paley (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Mariella Sala (Box 108)
  - Lucy Friedman, 1997 (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Hasna Mekdashi, 1997 (Box 108)
  - Arab women's conference, H. Mekdeshi (Box 108)
  - Asenath Odaga (Box 108)
  - Send to Meredith (Box 108)
  - Ninotchka Rosca, 1994-1997 (3 folders) (Box 109)
  - UN World Conference on Human Rights, Vienna, Austria, June 13-25, 1993 (Box 109)
  - Domna Conference/Michigan, 1998 (Box 109)
  - Mariella Sala Eguren, 1994 (Box 109)
  - Monika van Paemel, 1992-1997 (2 folders) (Box 109)
  - Domna Stanton (Box 109)
  - Budgets and worksheets, 1997 (Box 109)
  - NYC Board mtg., 1998 (Box 109)
  - Board mailing and quarterly financial report, 1997-1998 (3 folders) (Box 109)
  - Exec committee faxes and letters, 1997 (Box 109)
  - Memo: Urgent need to do a Women's WORLD Book, 1998 (Box 109)
  - Packet and PR Board packet for mtgs Antwerp (Box 109)
  - Women's WORLD board of directors meetings, 1994-1996 (8 folders) (Box 110)
  - Exec Committee Meeting, NYC, 1996 (Box 110)
  - Logos/letterhead drafts (Box 110)
  - Aicha mess, 1995 (Box 110)
  - Women's Liberation: Contradictions in-political (Box 111)
  - Women's Liberation: South (Box 111)
  - Women: Unions (Box 111)
  - Women studies (Box 111)
  - Women's Liberation: Trotskyist lit, not incl. SWP (Box 111)
  - SWP and Women (Box 111)
  - YAWF Women (2 folders) (Box 111)
  - Working Class Women's Movement (Box 111)
  - Women's Liberation: West (Box 111)
  - Women: Welfare (Box 111)
  - Women's Liberation: Women: Eastern Europe (Box 111)